banglagamer.com 2012-05-01

# BanglaGamer - Rule Book

  * Rule Book

* * *

Unregistered, You must accept the Forum Rules below to be able to use some forum functions. 

Rule Book 

General Rules (Collapsed)

Privacy Statement 

Here at Ice Network, we do respect your privacy. However, as we ask for some basic information about you during registration, we want you to be fully aware of how these information may be utilized.

**Registration in Ice Network**  
During registration in Ice Network, we ask for some basic personal information.  
You can control many aspects of your privacy through your user control panel located at top.  
Administrator(s) are be able to view all data and some higher level staffs will be able to view some portion of it.  
However, we will never sell your private data to anyone else. We will not disclose them in public unless it becomes a necessity (like law enforcement officials).

Please keep in mind that we may send your e-newsletter (promotional, non-promotional) to you using your email address.  
However, we will never disclose your email address to any third party.

**Information Ice Network Requests**  
When you register, you are asked to give demographic information (like birth year, occupation etc). We ask you to tell us a little about yourself so we can better understand the types of people who register. This information can also be used to provide you with content that may be of interest to you, and to show you advertisements that are relevant to your demographic information.

We might utilize outside ad companies to display ads on its sites. These ads may contain cookies. While we use cookies in other parts of its sites, the ad companies also use cookies with the ads displayed, and we may not have access to this information.

People of all age are accepted to resgister in Ice Network

**Security**  
Ice Network has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under its control.  
The server has strict security in place to prevent an intruder from retrieving personal information about its users.  
However, even the mightiest protection might kneel down to a crafty hacker/cracker. Therefore, we can not guarantee 100% security.

**Links and Content**  
The site may contain links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices, security, contents of such other sites.  
We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information.  
This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by Ice Network.

Ice Network will not be responsible for any links posted in here that refer/lead to any kind of political/personal violation, porno-graphical or any of the abuse to any person or group of person or to any race/region/religion.

**Summary**  
Ice Network is a public place. You come here on your own accord, you take the responsibilities for your actions.

In this electronic era, when personal information can easily be obtained through various sources, we appreciate the sensitivity of any private information that you disclose to us. It is our intention to treat your account information with the highest level of care. 

By registering in this site, you agree to all of the rules aforementioned and our Terms of Service (ToS).  
Appropriate action(s) will be taken against you for breaking/not obeying any part of it.  
All rules are meant to augment common sense, please use them when not conflicted with aforementioned policies. 

 I have read, and agree to abide by the BanglaGamer rules.
